(This program is intended
for viewers aged 18 and over.)
(It may contain content
depicting inappropriate behavior)
(violence, sexual content,
and strong language.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(This series is entirely fictional
and does not depict)
(any real individuals, locations,
organizations, or events.)
P'Three!
I forgot to bring my clothes in.
Could you grab them for me, please?
P'Three, why aren't you
wearing any clothes?
Why are you coming in?
I'm just bringing you your clothes.
What kind of dirty thoughts
are you having?
Shouldn't you go
put some clothes on first?
I'm gonna do some laundry.
Or do you think...
I'm going to do something to you?
And don't keep me waiting.
I'm showering after you.
Okay.
Hey.
What? Are you scared
I'll see your willy?
Please get out. I'm going to shower.
We've both got it. Why be embarrassed?
Maybe what's different
is the confidence level.
Whoa, hey, what are you trying to say?
- You're confident? Let me see.
- P'Three, get out!
- Are you really that confident?
- This isn't meant for...
- Get out!
- What?
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Every time, it's just me and me only♪
♪What's this feeling? I've got no clue,♪
♪Could it be I'm missing you?♪
♪(Am I missing you?)♪
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Why is it always happening to me?♪
♪The more it happens, the more I see♪
♪Yeah, it must be♪
P'Three's up early.
Yeah, move.
Finish them off.
Not bad at all.
- Sh*t!
- Oh...
You startled me.
I'm the one who's startled.
When did you get here?
Just a moment
before you started the match.
Did you wake up early,
or have you been up all night?
My biological clock
always wakes me up around this time.
My body is craving caffeine.
Morning coffee, you know?
Did you actually get some sleep?
How am I supposed to sleep?
Soh...
Seriously?
I'm gonna embarrass you
when you wake up.
I'll just go sleep
in the living room, then.
Or...
Was I moving around so much in my sleep
that you couldn't get any rest?
- I'm sorry.
- Hey, no. No.
It's just...
my body's full of energy,
so I had to get up early
and get some practice in.
Practice over, energy spent.
Better top up with some coffee.
Whoa, are you drinking two cups?
Your heart might race.
Just a little coffee
won't affect my heart
as much as being near you.
Oh...
So, sleeping next to me last night...
made your heart race so much
that you couldn't sleep,
right?
Man, you're getting good
at these cheesy jokes, aren't you?
Go.
Go shower and brush your teeth.
I already squeezed
the toothpaste out for you.
And I'll take you to your condo.
Roger that.
Soh, I'll see you again this evening.
I'm taking you to the training camp.
Training camp?
Yeah.
Hello, everyone.
Today, welcome to "Blue Viper Time."
It's me, Peem.
Guys, the Pro League
is just around the corner,
so I'd like to show you
our training camp
to see what the vibe is like here.
In this first zone,
they're working really hard.
It's a place
for all our players to practice.
You're practicing
quite intensely, right, Meen?
- Yes, we are.
- Am I interrupting?
No.
Oh, okay.
How's it going? Busy practicing?
- Yeah. We have to...
- You're checking the enemy's strategy?
Whoa. Alright,
I'd better not disturb her.
She's super focused.
Anyway, let's see what ALONEW is doing.
- Hello.
- How are things, our MVP?
- Practicing with a new hero.
- A new hero? Wow.
Oops, am I spoiling the plan?
Will this be released
before or after the match?
I'd better not bother him.
Let him focus
on the new hero he's practicing with.
The next zone is for the coach.
I have to keep my voice down,
or the coach will scold me.
He analyzes the strategies
for both our team...
and the opposing team.
He gives excellent advice
to the Blue Viper players.
That's why Blue Viper
is a title contender every year.
It's only to be expected,
especially with me around.
Alright, let's move on to the next zone.
This is the chill zone
where we have various games to play
besides the one we compete in.
- And there's a sitting area...
- Wait,
does a training camp
have to be this fancy?
Of course.
This is Blue Viper's camp, man.
They're the undefeated kings
of the Pro League
who have won almost every year.
They've got tens of millions
invested in the team.
I bet these players
are making six figures.
I knew gaming could make you money,
but I didn't think
it would be this much.
Man, the Pro League is no joke.
It's where the country's top players
face off against each other.
And you're about to be one of them.
Holy sh*t!
Our friend is going to be
a full-time esports athlete soon.
That's so cool.
With good food
and a nice place like this,
I could practice all day long.
Me, too.
Welcome to the B.S. Brothers' camp!
There it is.
Oh, for God's sake.
You made such a grand entrance,
but this place is a total sh*thole.
Hey, make yourselves at home.
Just think of this as your second home.
Okay.
Let me give you a tour.
This room right here
is what we call "The Base."
It's a very important room
because all our strategies and plans
can never leak out from here.
They must stay within these walls.
Why do you have to be so dramatic?
Just call it what it is,
the training room.
Now, if you want to relax,
there's an internet cafe downstairs.
After gaming, you might get tired
and feel like you're dying, right?
Just head next door.
The massage lady there
has hands of gold.
Our team gets three meals a day.
The food's cooked by P'Jane.
Trust me, it's damn delicious.
If you don't believe me, here's proof.
Just check out P'Toobtub's body.
That's all the proof you need.
If you're worried
about gaining weight, don't be
because we have...
a mini-gym.
Okay.
Anyway, that's enough
for the introductions.
Alright? Let's go practice.
- Let's go, baby. Let's go.
- Hold on!
Hey, newbie.
Since you stepped into this room,
have you greeted the owner yet?
The owner?
- Who is it?
- Jeez.
- He's right here.
- Right here.
This used to be
P'Toobtub's grandma's room.
She was bedridden for years.
After she passed away in that bed,
we turned it into this training camp.
But I've heard some things.
Your team's situation
isn't looking too good.
You guys are at the bottom
of the league,
and your teammates play like trash.
They end up in last place every year.
It's a total disaster waiting to happen.
Honestly, they're definitely
using you to carry them.
You're in for a rough time, buddy.
Anyway, just think of it as your debut.
Maybe another team
will scout you and sign you.
Right?
(One month before the Pro League)
We've got everything here.
The whole team's here, you know?
- P'Laem, don't be scared. Dive in!
- Yeah!
- Here. Right here.
- I know, I know!
- No, right here.
- Jeez!
Dammit! If you don't stop,
I'm gonna kick both your asses.
You're both getting it now.
Get over here!
- P'Soh!
- Hey...
Help me, P'Soh!
Hey, watch it, Derpy Kid!
(First Blood)
Good thing I tanked that damage in time.
- Guys!
- Come on!
Time for Laem's solo!
Go ahead, let it all out.
A defensive item with full coverage.
Hey, Soh, fall back. You're gonna die.
Man, we're toast.
Losing nonstop like this
is just too much.
I think we should go with Plan M.
Huh?
Again?
I...
It's my fault.
I'm sorry...
The mookrata plan!
Look, Plan M works every time.
One round of mookrata. Let's go.
- Go, go, go. Hurry!
- Mookrata!
Come on, Three, Soh.
Hey, don't worry.
That was just a warm-up.
Let's go grab some mookrata instead.
Hey, don't worry about it.
Gaming is supposed to be fun.
Dive in. Go, go!
Hey!
- P'Jack...
- Jeez!
- Ew.
- You guys are overreacting.
It's just my allergies.
I don't want to take any risks.
Here, take this.
- Wow, look at you.
- Hey!
If you get sick and miss practice,
our team's performance won't just drop.
It'll go straight to hell.
For God's sake.
Why so dramatic?
Wait, Soh's not here yet?
I haven't seen him.
He's probably just late.
I saw him streaming yesterday
after practice.
He wasn't going to quit until he won,
but he was on a serious losing streak.
He's not home
crying his eyes out right now, is he?
Come on.
(Hello, P'Three?)
Hey, are you crying?
- See? Told ya.
- He really is crying.
How are you feeling, sick guy?
P'Three?
Why did you buy so much stuff?
Oh, I just brought you
some healing items.
I'm actually feeling better already.
You don't have to do all this for me.
Oh, come on, kiddo.
I just got here,
and you're already kicking me out?
Not even a thank-you.
I just didn't want to be a bother.
Stop talking and just eat.
Here, have some. Eat up...
so you can take your meds afterwards.
I'll do it myself.
Here, I bought some medicine, too.
This one's for your runny nose.
Take it after meals.
And...
this one's probably for your cough.
Take it before meals.
When should you take this one?
After meals.
How do you know?
Uh...
My mom's a doctor.
She stocked up
on plenty of medicine over there.
But I've taken most of them,
so they're almost gone.
It's actually great
that you bought some to restock for me.
You're so kind, P'Three.
Well, isn't that obvious?
Everyone says I'm a walking red flag,
but I'm actually greener
than the Amazon.
Not to brag or anything.
Here, turn around.
It's secure now.
Here's my first thank-you.
Thank you for coming to see me.
Otherwise, I would've had to
crawl down to get food myself.
Now, my second thank-you.
Thank you for buying me all this food.
Everything you bought for me...
looked so delicious.
And this is the third thank-you.
Thank you for getting me the medicine.
Now I have enough meds
to last me a decade.
You'd better give me
a fourth thank-you, too.
Because I'm gonna stay
and sponge you down until morning.
Here.
Ouch. P'Three, ow!
Ow!
If you're gonna do it this hard,
give me back my thank-you.
Look at you, whining so much.
But when you take heavy damage in-game,
I don't hear you complaining one bit.
Well, I'm sick right now.
What?
Didn't you just say you were all better?
Were you lying to me?
That's not very nice, you know.
Not nice at all.
- I'm sorry.
Oh...
Why are you apologizing to me?
You're just sponging me down.
It's not like I'm bleeding.
Then why are you apologizing to me?
Do you think
I was scolding you for real?
Well...
I haven't been able
to help the team at all,
and I even got sick on top of that.
Hey, don't blame yourself like that.
It's actually my fault
for not taking better care of you.
Besides, my team
didn't even have things figured out,
yet I still went and brought you in.
The truth is...
I just wanted everyone
to play together and have fun.
I'm not even expecting to win anymore.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
(Four, the Favorite Son)
Took you long enough to call back, huh?
(I'm not in the mood to fight, Four.)
Just say what you have to say.
Mom told me to call and ask
if you're coming home
for Dad's birthday next week.
I'm busy.
Seriously, though,
are you going to avoid Mom and Dad
for the rest of your life?
I'm actually busy.
I have to practice for the Pro League.
At your age...
(Do you still think
you can be a champion?)
Hey, age doesn't matter.
As long as I can play,
I'm going to keep playing.
You, Mom, and Dad
don't have to believe in me.
I'll just win and show you.
(Morning, P'Three.)
(I have a morning mission
for you today. Ready, go!)
What is he up to now?
(New day, HP's still low)
(Which item will you choose between...)
(A: If you need caffeine immediately,)
(head to
the resurrection potion extractor.)
(B: If food doesn't matter
and looking good comes first,)
(head to the magic mirror.)
The resurrection potion extractor?
(This cup restores +50% HP.)
(Next mission...)
(A: Want something to eat?)
(B: Check the news first?)
(My secret recipe
ham and cheese sandwich)
(loaded with gooey cheese
restores +100% HP.)
A secret recipe, huh?
(HP is full.
Let's do the final mission.)
(Time for the computer.)
Time for the computer?
What now?
(You can use the computer.
I didn't set a password.)
(There's a key in the drawer)
(in case you want to go out.)
(I'm tutoring with James and Arm today.)
(Might be back a bit late,
but don't worry.)
(Mr. Bear will be here
to keep you company.)
(Good Morning Thailand by Soh)
(Good Morning Thailand by Soh.)
(Weather Forecast:)
(You're awake.)
(It's a good sign to start a new day.)
(The weather is bright today.)
(Perfect for squeezing in
a practice match.)
(Breaking News: One easy target
has been found)
(reading this message.)
(Today's Career Horoscope:)
(It's definitely going to be
a good and smooth day.)
(No matter what you face,
I want you to know...)
(that I'm right here rooting for you.)
(Good luck! From Soh.)
Whoa, Derpy Kid.
Dammit.
Am I smiling right now?
You're a mess.
Did you practice so hard
that you got this sick?
Exams are coming up, man.
If you can't handle it,
just withdraw.
I'm fine. I can handle it.
Don't worry. You're already smart.
Arm will tutor you for a bit,
and you'll get it in no time.
Wait, wait.
Am I seeing things?
That's P'Three, right?
What is he doing here?
Did you come to see me
for something urgent?
Oh...
Oh, well, I came...
to ask you to pick out a gift with me
for P'Toobtub's baby.
Wanna come along?
I do.
I just finished tutoring.
Let's go, shall we?
Sure.
You don't have to carry my bag for me.
I can carry it myself.
Uh, well, I...
No... Never mind.
Shall we go buy it now?
Or we'll be late for the training camp.
Okay.
You're thinking
what I'm thinking, right?
Don't you think it's a bit weird?
Are you thinking the same thing?
What are you thinking?
Something's definitely off.
Oh...
Hey, thanks.
Hey, *sshole! That's mine.
- Why are you drinking that?
- Can't I have a sip?
- You have your own.
- But I wanted green tea.
(Coaching Conversation)
(Parenting)
You're really serious, aren't you?
It's just a gift for the baby.
Well, I'm just excited.
I can't wait to read bedtime stories
to the baby.
I'm confused.
Why are you so hyped up?
It's because I'm an only child.
Whenever it's about kids, I...
get really invested.
It's kind of strange, isn't it?
An only child wants siblings,
while those with siblings...
wish they were an only child.
I think you're lucky, though.
It's like having a best friend
who's grown up with you since day one.
You might fight or argue sometimes,
but you're still on the same team.
Wait,
were you eavesdropping on my call?
But I didn't want to fight anymore,
so I moved out to live on my own,
doing things my parents think
are a waste of time.
And my younger brother
probably thinks I'm a loser.
But I've made up my mind
that I won't go back.
Not until I can buy a house,
get a car,
and have millions in savings.
Then I'll go show off
right in front of my parents,
so they'll finally stop
looking down on me.
Don't you ever get homesick, though?
Of course I do.
Don't you try
to talk me into going back.
I've already decided.
That's not what I meant.
I understand
that your goals are important, too.
But even if you don't go yourself,
you can still send a gift, right?
Will it really work, Derpy Kid?
My family owns a gold store.
They're way richer than me.
They wouldn't care
about shoes like these.
If it were an expensive watch,
that'd be a different story.
The best things
don't have to be expensive.
Whoa, whoa. Hey.
You don't have to.
So,
is this how Cinderella feels?
All done, P'Three.
Stand up and try walking in them.
Whoa.
These are so comfortable.
Is this how the heroes feel
when they get god-tier boots?
Of course, P'Three.
When you wear good shoes,
it prevents your feet from aching.
And when you walk a lot,
it prevents back pain, too.
That's why I buy them
for my mom all the time.
Good health...
is something no amount of money can buy.
I hope my parents and Four
will like them.
(We are B.S. Brothers)
Here it is.
Thanks a lot, Soh.
The baby is still
just an embryo, though.
Why are you in such a rush
to buy things?
Wait.
P'Three said you wanted a gift
for the baby already.
Hold on a second.
So P'Three...
told Soh he wanted
to buy something for P'Toobtub?
And the two of you
went shopping alone together?
Huh?
Well...
I've heard P'Toobtub
complaining quite a lot
about needing to put all his money
back into the shop.
And with the baby coming soon,
he'd have to buy baby stuff, too.
So we just wanted to help
lighten the load.
Wait, Three, when did I
ever complain to you?
You did say it!
Oh, right, yeah.
I guess I did say that.
I really wanted it, right?
The one I sent you in the chat.
- That's great.
- Yeah, bro.
- Thanks a lot, my dear bros.
- Don't mention it.
Anyway, are you all better now, Soh?
Yes, I'm all better.
I'm sorry to everyone
for missing practice for so many days.
But I promise
that I'll hurry
and catch up with all of you.
I definitely won't drag the team down.
It's fine.
No need to be so serious
about stuff like this.
Our team is cursed anyway.
No matter how we play,
we never make it to the finals.
I'm not surprised
P'Pech wants to disband the team.
What?
That's some bad luck talk right there.
What Laem said might sound harsh,
but I've prepared myself
for the worst, too.
It's true that
our team had its glory days,
but look at how old we are now.
Who knows if we can even keep up
with the younger players.
I think this tournament
might be the last one for us.
Come on.
What's up with that?
I was in such a good mood today.
You just made me so depressed.
If this is going to be
our last tournament,
shall we give it everything we've got?
Hey,
how long has it been
since we were at the top?
I miss the view from up there.
Shall we try one more time
to go breathe that summit air?
Yeah, that's the spirit,
Son of Wanphen!
Dude, I don't mind you
making fun of my mom's name.
But if you don't play like a beast
on match day,
I'm definitely smacking your head.
- Bring it on!
- Just you wait. I'll...
Stop!
Let's do a team huddle.
- Talk your sh*t, take the championship!
I really want to breathe
that air up top.
- Wow, so refreshing.
- How is it?
Refreshing, man. So refreshing.
We've gotta get back up there
to breathe that air.
Exactly.
Oh, you're back, son?
You're back so late today.
Have you eaten anything yet?
Yes, Mom.
Look at this.
Today, I was going through
some old things
as I was planning to
sell them by weight,
and I found
your high school friendship journal.
Right, how is Ten doing?
Ever since you graduated from college,
I haven't seen him
come visit our house at all.
He's just busy with work, Mom.
I've been pretty busy myself.
We haven't talked much.
So, I'm going up to take a shower now.
(To Jack, my lovely friend.
Hi, Jack, I'm Noey from Class 6/3.)
(Congrats on getting into college.
Hope to see you again.)
(Wishing you happiness and good friends.
I'm glad we're friends.)
(To Jack, my best friend. From Ten,
the friend who loves you the most.)
(I hope you live a happy life)
(and get to do everything you want.
I'm so glad I met you.)
(Wanna play ranked?)
(Thanks for carrying me again.)
(If you hadn't healed me
in that last second,)
(I'd definitely be dead.)
(I'm used to carrying you by now.)
(Going to sleep now.)
(Oh, and I'm pretty busy lately.)
(I might not be able to
play ranked with you much.)
(Are you training
for the Pro League or something?)
(Probably not. You play like trash.)
(You never know.)
(You might be carrying
an esports pro right now.)
(Why are you being so mysterious?)
(I'm getting scared.)
(Who am I actually friends with here?)
Let's meet up when we're free.
I want to meet you in person, too.
P'Pech gave us the orders.
We've gotta...
win the first match to set the tone
and gain momentum to get the advantage.
Yes, let's do this!
- Let's go.
- Come on.
- Let's do it.
But you're facing Kingdom
in the first match.
- Oh, come on!
- What?
What the hell?
I'm not playing.
Change the game.
Calm down.
If you can beat the first team,
it'll be a great start.
But even if you don't win,
you still have a chance
to redeem yourselves.
Don't stress about it.
If you're under too much pressure,
the team might lose their nerve,
and it won't be good.
Just play according to your usual form,
but you have to stay focused.
Focus. Keep that in mind.
I'm already shook
just hearing the team's name.
We're doomed.
It's a total nightmare.
We've played 14 matches
and lost all 14 of them.
It's like they've got us
all figured out.
Hey,
but this time,
things are gonna be different
because we've got a joker up our sleeve.
They'll never see us coming.
Me?
Yeah.
The secret weapon.
What a huge surprise!
Here's B.S. Brothers' lineup
for this season,
featuring their brand-new Support,
Derya MK12!
Whoa, that name?
I bet the shippers
are screaming right now.
They're going to be losing it
as the fan-favorite ship, Three and Soh,
is finally on display.
Wow, they're really well-known.
We'll have to see
just how much of a change
Derya will bring to the team,
especially in this first match
where they face Kingdom,
one of the top-tier teams
from last year, man.
Will they be able to handle it, P'Win?
Looking at the buzz in our community,
(3-0 for sure, no doubt)
it's looking like a total sweep.
(Losers are just losers)
It's a sweep.
(Derya who? Never heard of him)
It's definitely gonna be 3-0.
Now the question is can B.S. Brothers
prove the doubters wrong?
We'll just have to wait and see.
Today's the day everyone finds out
that B.S. Brothers
is more than just talk.
(See you at the studio
after the exam.)
(No rush.)
(We've got plenty of time
to put on a show for them today.)
(Listen up, everyone.)
(The 14-0 record of B.S. Brothers)
(is definitely going to happen again)
(because they're unlucky enough)
(to run into Kingdom
in the first match.)
Oh, but right now,
there's a bit of buzz going around,
whispering that
a new member named Derya MK12
might turn things around,
but who knows if he actually can.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on a second, bro.
We've got an insider.
(Someone sent me a video
of B.S. Brothers practicing.)
(Let's take a look at it first.)
- (Mid skills, just clout chasers.)
- Jeez, kid.
What kind of play is that?
(He's got nothing special.)
You're better off staying home.
(Without Three, nobody would've cared.)
Don't think B.S. Brothers will make it.
(He's even afraid
to take off his head mask.)
(Scared of being embarrassed
when you lose, huh? LOL)
(Donating a hundred.)
(Need some friends to jump him
and rip that bear head off.)
(I hate those who try too hard
to have a gimmick.)
(The team would be better off
without him.)
(Want to bet that Derya
will definitely cost them the game?)
(D-Day)
Sh*t, this is bad.
Guys, check this out.
- (Such a noob.)
- Sh*t.
The haters are swarming in.
Soh is getting trashed.
What should we do?
If Soh sees this,
he won't be able to handle it.
I bet he's already seen it.
The video just blew up.
He's still not here,
and the match is about to begin.
B.S. Brothers, please stand by.
Give us a second, please.
How's it going, Three?
The match is starting, man.
Hey, Nuii, Pod, settle it with
a game of rock, paper, scissors.
Winner subs in for Soh.
Yeah.
Do it.
Yeah, go.
Here we go.
Today's my day to shine.
Guys, give it your all. We have to win.
Come on, come on. First game, let's go.
(All Creeps Deployed)
- Let's trail them first.
- Got it.
Wait...
What the hell was that?
Isn't that a bit too fast?
Sorry.
- Try again. Focus!
- Okay.
Hey, the Support isn't that good.
- Looking good. This is easy.
- Wow, just one minute in.
and we've already got First Blood.
Nuii just got taken out.
He mispositioned himself,
and it showed.
Wow, they're being chased down hard.
Pod and Nuii are under heavy pressure.
They're literally running
behind the tower.
This looks like an early game disaster.
They probably won't make it.
Sh*t, where the hell is Soh?
Maybe he couldn't take it
and withdrew before the match?
Then what are we gonna do?
How would I know?
P'Three?
Are you doing okay, kiddo?
What are you doing here?
What about the match?
Well, I saw your HP dropping,
so I teleported here to heal you.
Is this your first time getting trashed?
Freaked out, didn't you?
Yeah.
But I understand.
My dad once told me that...
people who aren't hated
are the ones who are invisible.
I'm not invisible.
That's why I get hated on.
I get it.
I've dealt with it my whole life, too.
I even wondered,
"What the hell did I ever do to them?"
But as I got older, I realized
you can't make everyone like you.
And to be fair,
I can be kind of an *sshole sometimes.
All I can do now
is choose what to focus on.
It's the same for you, Derpy Kid.
Just focus on the people
who actually care about you.
The people who care about me?
You don't have to look very far.
I'm right here.
I mean...
Me and the B.S. Brothers members.
As for those who don't like us,
there's nothing we can do
to change their minds.
But think about it.
If their lives were actually going well,
why would they spend their time
trashing us
just to make themselves feel better?
Whatever your reason was
for coming here,
thank you.
And...
I'm sorry
for causing such a mess.
I shouldn't have put you
through all this trouble.
(Today's mission is
to choose what your heart desires.)
(A: Recall. Open the door
and we'll fight this out together.)
(B: Surrender. Just tell me.
I'll understand and walk away.)
(P.S. Either way,
I'm always by your side.)
I came here
just to make sure you're still okay.
If you can't handle it,
or if you're not ready to go back,
it's totally fine. I understand.
Right now, your feelings
are what matter most.
You got that, kiddo?
So, you okay?
(The Blue Team's tower
has been destroyed)
We can end it.
- Hurry, hurry!
- Go for it. Let's end this!
Nice!
We got this. One more game.
Nice.
I'm sorry.
What the hell?
Yeah, what the hell is this?
What is wrong with you guys?
And that's the end of the second game.
Kingdom has taken a 2-0 lead.
Wow, this is exactly
what many people expected.
They can't seem to put up a fight,
and this is going to be a crucial game.
If they can't make a comeback here,
they're going out of business
at this rate.
I'm frustrated.
Looking at you two
is making me frustrated.
P'Toobtub,
do you have a backup plan?
Plan A, Plan B, Plan C,
or X, Y, Z, or whatever...
You got anything?
What should we do?
It doesn't look like
we're gonna make it.
Let me think for a second.
The Jungler isn't here.
The Support hasn't shown up.
I'm going crazy.
Dammit.
It's okay.
B.S. Brothers,
please get ready for the third game.
Just a moment, please.
Break time is over.
You need to come immediately.
Okay, we'll be right there.
What the hell are we gonna do?
It's alright.
This is insane.
Alright, let's go.
There's nothing left to lose now.
It's time to go all out.
Let's go, everyone!
- Come on, let's go.
- Come on.
Let's go do what we love.
Come on.
- Talk your sh*t, take the championship!
Let's do this.
Whoa...
There he is.
My savior has arrived!
Alright, we're back for the third game.
It's match point for Kingdom,
and it looks like B.S. Brothers
isn't going down without a fight
even though the odds
are heavily against them.
At this point,
- Kingdom might be in trouble now.
- Here I am.
No one can take me down.
Jeez.
Run it back.
It's okay. Let's go again.
Wow, what an incredible play!
Derya just saved the captain's life.
The synergy between Thr33 and Derya
is incredible.
They are perfectly in sync.
I bet Kingdom must be
shaking in their boots
as the precision of the gameplay
coming from these two
is truly terrifying.
This is basically over.
Push, push, push!
(Blue Team has summoned Super Creeps)
Easy.
Easy!
B.S. Brothers made a comeback
and won the third game!
- Unbelievable.
- I've no idea how they pulled that off.
They've clawed their way
back to 1-2 now.
It's hard to believe,
but it just happened.
Yeah, Laem, go for it!
- You got it, bro.
- Yeah, that was damn cool.
And we're back for the fourth game.
Wow, Derya is incredibly calm.
It's almost scary.
He's one hundred percent
focused on the game.
He's so calm
I thought he wasn't even moving.
Whoa, is he a JPEG or something?
What an outstanding performance
from Derya.
He really is the secret weapon
just like they say.
Whoa, why'd they dive like that?
Group up at their base. All in!
Come on, everyone. Come over here.
Oh, easy. This is too easy, folks.
And they've successfully tied it up!
2-2, I can't believe it.
B.S. Brothers have dragged Kingdom
into the fifth game,
the decider.
That's no small feat.
Preaw, push the bottom lane.
I'll handle the top.
- I'm on it.
- Laem, go mid.
No need for help.
I'm taking this one myself.
- Looks like he wants to solo.
- This one's mine.
- I got this.
- They're here!
- Get them.
- Follow them.
Nice, just like that.
- Alright, let's go.
- Are we going in?
- Go, go. On my way.
- Here we go.
- They're flanking. Defend mid.
- Alright, here we go.
This is the final team fight,
and Kingdom is trying
to shut everything down.
But everything is out of control.
They're trying to take Derya down,
but that's not going to be easy.
Whoa, Derya is still alive!
He's successfully bought some time,
and Thr33 is back.
- Got it. Wow, a Quad Kill!
- End it.
- End the game!
- This is definitely it.
(Cannon Minion have spawned)
- Over here.
- Bring it on!
B.S. Brothers won the final team fight.
It's unbelievable!
They finally broke the 14-0 curse.
Wow, they cheated death
and made an insane comeback to win 3-2.
That's what I'm talking about.
Nailed it. I'm loving this!
- Soh won!
- He did it.
They're here.
We've got the RPL ticket for you, bro.
Well done, everyone. Great job.
RPL!
- RPL!
Hey, wait.
Soh, why are you looking so sad?
We won, man! Aren't you happy?
I...
I'm so sorry.
If only I'd gotten here sooner...
Come with me.
Hey, why are you guys looking so sad?
We won!
- RPL!
Derpy Kid, did you know?
According to scientists,
a hug...
makes you happier.
I'm going to count to three.
If you don't rush over here
to recharge your happiness battery,
you're gonna miss your chance.
One,
two,
three...
I'm sorry.
I almost ruined everything.
I know, I know.
I won't do it again.
I promise.
I know.
I'm getting tired of your apologies.
Can't you say anything else?
I...
love you, P'Three.
What?
What...
What did you say?
I said...
I love you, P'Three.
You're my MVP today.
Hey, wait a second.
Did I tie it too tight?
Wait, tie what?
With a name like Soh,
you should say "chain."
Not funny?
Your name means chain,
and it can be used as a verb as well.
I see.
Man, your reaction
just killed my confidence.
I shouldn't have made that joke.
So it should be...
Chaining Three to Soh, right?
Whoa!
I like that.
Well,
now I want to be chained up.